Anthony Roybal

Software Developer

roybal.usmc@gmail.com

909-936-7765

Irvine, CA

linkedin.com/in/anthony-roybal in

Passionate Software Developer with 2 years experience using Unity and C# in personal projects, seeking a Quality Assurance position. Team player with a positive attitude and a hunger to learn and develop. Accountable, solution seeking leader, with the ability to go above and beyond to meet deadlines. Also, has experience using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript for Front-End Development.

SKILLS



WORK EXPERIENCE

Quality Assurance Analyst

Blizzard Entertainment

09/2019 – Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Worked collaboratively with QA team and QA Leads to complete comprehensive testing on a major new release of Warcraft 3.
- Documented software defects using Jira bug tracking system and reported defects involving asset functionality, visualization and content to artists and developers.
- Documented Test Cases using TestRail test management tool during the Software Development Life Cycle to track progress and meet deadlines.

Game Tester

Netmarble

01/2018 – 01/2019 Los Angeles, CA

Achievements/Tasks

- Analyzed pre and post released products that had newly added content.
- Provided feed back on products to include bugs, UI issues, issues with game mechanics in order to improve current features.
- Worked on single day projects and on an as needed basis.

Quality Assurance Tester

Escape Games VR

09/2016 – 10/2016 Irvine, CA

Achievements/Tasks

- Analyzed products, documented and tracked bugs, as well as tested newly implemented designs.
- Installed and configured computer systems to include hardware and software for Clients who purchased VR packages.
- Collaborated with development team on new implementations and designs for future projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Administrative Specialist Supervisor

U.S. Marine Corps

06/2014 - 03/2016

- Achievements/Tasks
- Managed 8 personnel that provided customer service dealing with pay, orders, and travel arrangements using the Defense Travel System.
- Managed and tracked travel arrangements, delinquency reports, including analyzing expenses for over 900 employees.
- Designed and implanted new tracking system for travel arrangements and expenses, which resulted in an increase of efficiency by 12%.
- Managed a team that prepared the Defense Travel System for inspection, that resulted in achieving a "100% compliance".

Infantry Team Leader/Rifleman

U.S. Marine Corps

03/2011 - 06/2014

- Achievements/Tasks
- Managed 3 personnel in order to increase proficiency in infantry tactics, physical fitness and tactical exercises.
- As a Martial Arts Instructor, increased company combat readiness up to Marine Corps standards by developing and training personnel using the Marine Corps Martial Arts Program.
- Achieved Proficiency in multiple weapon systems, non-lethal tactics, and hand-to-hand combat at the brown belt level.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Alien Attack (C# Unity Engine) (07/2018 – 09/2018)

Prevent the aliens from abducting their cattle.

Alien Escape (C# Unity Engine) (01/2018 – 05/2018)

- 2.5D side scroller to avoid obstacles to get from the starting platform to the finish platform.
- -View website for more projects

CERTIFICATES

Learn Modern OpenGL Programming Course (11/2018) Shader Development For Unity With CG (11/2018)

Lua Programming With LOVE (05/2019)

Data Structures And Singly Linked List (05/2019)

-more on LinkedIn Profile

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Science Visual and Game Programming

The Art Institute of California

04/2016 - 03/2019

Associates of Science in Computer Applications and Programming

ITT Technical Institute

2002 - 2004